# Kavitha Ariyabandu

137/2 Soi Sai Namthip 2, Sukhumvit 22, Bangkok 10110
<a href="mailto:ariyabandu@outlook.com">ariyabandu@outlook.com</a>
+66860736852

## Profile

Three years experience within the corporate banking sector overseeing front office and operations through substantial product enhancement and project management work. Working with a leading global corporate bank has enlightened me on multi-cultural work environments within the Asia Pacific region. The interactions have given me a sense of timeliness and efficiency, which has shaped me to become a candidate capable of delivering results.

## Key Skills & Strengths

- Product Enhancement
- Market Research/Analysis
- Data Compilation/Analysis
- Presentation Composition
- MI Report Publication

- Interdepartmental Coordination
- Personable Communicator
- Proficient Multitasker
- Tactful Negotiator
- Commercial Versatility

# Professional Experience

## The Royal Bank of Scotland (RBS)

## **Thailand**

#### **Country Project Manager**

March 2015 - Present

- Coordinated with all local teams to develop a strategic branch closure plan.
- Executed the full front to back branch closure plan with minimum execution risk. The execution consists
  of:
  - Coordinating with all departments to draft the closure proposal to submit to the Bank of Thailand.
  - Communicating with client teams to effectively exit the client portfolio in periodic waves.
  - Coordinating with local and regional product teams for a systematic product shutdown.
  - Organising weekly forums with local and regional partners to track project progress and providing the platform for each business function to share knowledge on project issues.

#### **Product Analyst**

January 2014 - February 2015

- Coordinated with local operations and regional technology teams to launch a remittance product from development stage to the initial transaction stage.
- Coordinated with product development teams to support enhancements in current products for a better increase in product process efficiency.
- Successfully setup operations process, trained staff and established the SOP for a Cash Pooling product.
- Through monitoring transaction datasets, opportunities in pricing gaps were identified within cash management products to implement stringent pricing strategies to prevent any financial loss.

## International Union for Conservation of Nature (IUCN) Thailand

#### **Project Intern - Human Resources**

October - December 2013

- Analysed the local Conditions of Services and the IUCN Asia Rule book based on revisions by regional HR teams.
- Coordinated with Regional HR teams to identify specific local changes as opposed to the generic changes

## The Royal Bank of Scotland (RBS)

**Thailand** 

#### **Management Intern - Global Transaction Services**

January - July 2013

- Coordinated with RBS Japan to identify potential Japanese subsidiaries in Thailand with parent companies in Japan to establish new local relationships.
- Formulated a Business plan with a 3-year financial and strategic forecast for the Transaction Services department.
- Formulated the RBS Thailand country flash report coordination with all departments in the bank; the report
  included the performance and strategy of each division within the bank which was then circulated to the regional
  headquarters in Singapore.

TATA Motors Thailand

#### **Intern - Human Resources**

July - September 2010

- Communicated with all front office department heads and the TATA motors manufacturing plant to identify a list of learning and development needs while differentiating and accommodating for specific departments.
- Produced the learning and development calendar depicting the competency areas that require additional training as well as denote the specific job roles and employees that require additional training, the time period in which the training could be conducted and the recommended third party agencies to conduct in-house training.

# The United Nations International Strategy for Disaster Reduction (UNISDR)

**Switzerland** 

Intern May – August 2008

- Assisted in research and data collection on the Public-Private Partnership project for Disaster Risk Reduction.
- Assisted in developing a database on major disaster events in selected countries.

Education

## Royal Holloway University of London, UK

2011-2012

### **MSc International Human Resource Management**

MSc dissertation: Conducted research on how cultural factors can influence cultural training programs with a sample of employees from the United Nations Secretariat in Bangkok, Thailand.

## Kingston University London, UK

2008-2011

**BA (Hons) in Business Management** 

References

References available upon request

For more details please refer to: https://th.linkedin.com/in/kavithaariyabandu